{
	"totalQuizzes": 1,
	"quizzes": [{
				"quizName": "Data Structure Quiz",
				"quizQuestions": [{
						"question": "Which one of the following is an application of Stack Data Structure?",
						"answer": 3,
						"options": [
							"Managing function calls",
							"The stock span problem",
							"Arithmetic expression evaluation",
							"All of the above"
						]
					},
					{
						"question": "Which one of the following is an application of Queue Data Structure?",
						"answer": 3,
						"options": [
							"When a resource is shared among multiple consumers.",
							"When data is transferred asynchronously (data not necessarily received at same rate as sent) ",
							"Load Balancing",
							"All of the above"
						]
					},
					{
						"question": "Which of the following sorting algorithms can be used to sort a random linked list with minimum time complexity?",
						"answer": 3,
						"options": [
							"Insertion Sort",
							"Quick Sort",
							"Heap Sort",
							"Merge Sort"
						]
					},
					{
						"question": "Which of the following is true about linked list implementation of stack?",
						"answer": 3,
						"options": [
							"Min push operation, if new nodes are inserted at the beginning of linked list, then in pop operation, nodes must be removed from end.",
							"In push operation, if new nodes are inserted at the end, then in pop operation, nodes must be removed from the beginning.",
							"Both of the above",
							"None of the above"
						]
					},
					{
						"question": "Which of the following is an advantage of adjacency list representation over adjacency matrix representation of a graph?",
						"answer": 3,
						"options": [
							"In adjacency list representation, space is saved for sparse graphs.",
							"DFS and BSF can be done in O(V + E) time for adjacency list representation. These operations take O(V^2) time in adjacency matrix representation. Here is V and E are number of vertices and edges respectively.",
							"Adding a vertex in adjacency list representation is easier than adjacency matrix representation.",
							"All of the above"
						]
					}
				],
				"quizTotalNumbers": 5
		},
		{
			"quizName": "Computer Networks Quiz",
			"quizQuestions": [{
				"question": "What does PoP stand for?",
				"answer": 1,
				"options": [
					"Pre Office Protocol",
					"Post Office Protocol",
					"Protocol of Post",
					"None"
				]
			},
				{
					"question": "What is the port number of PoP?",
					"answer": 2,
					"options": [
						"35",
						"43",
						"110",
						"25"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "What is the number of layers in the OSI model?",
					"answer": 2,
					"options": [
						"2 layers",
						"4 layers",
						"7 layers",
						"9 layers"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "The full form of OSI is?",
					"answer": 3,
					"options": [
						"Operating System interface",
						"Optical System interconnection",
						"Operating System Internet",
						"Open system interconnection"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "Identify the layer which provides service to the user.",
					"answer": 1,
					"options": [
						"Session layer",
						"Application layer",
						"Presentation layer",
						"Physical layer"
					]
				}
			],
			"quizTotalNumbers": 5
		},
		{
			"quizName": "DBMS Quiz",
			"quizQuestions": [{
				"question": "Which of the following is the full form of DDL?",
				"answer": 0,
				"options": [
					"Data definition language",
					"Data derivation language",
					"Dynamic data language",
					"Detailed data language"
				]
			},
				{
					"question": "Which of the following is the property of transaction that protects data from system failure?",
					"answer": 2,
					"options": [
						"Atomicity",
						"Isolation",
						"Durability",
						"Consistency"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which of the following is preserved in execution of transaction in isolation??",
					"answer": 3,
					"options": [
						"Atomicity",
						"Isolation",
						"Durability",
						"Consistency"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which normalization form is based on the transitive dependency?",
					"answer": 2,
					"options": [
						"1NF",
						"2NF",
						"3NF",
						"BCNF"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which is the lowest level of abstraction that describes how the data are actually stored?",
					"answer": 1,
					"options": [
						"Physical",
						"Abstract",
						"View",
						"User"
					]
				}
			],
			"quizTotalNumbers": 5
		},
		{
			"quizName": "Machine Learning Quiz",
			"quizQuestions": [{
				"question": "Among the following option identify the one which is not a type of learning.",
				"answer": 0,
				"options": [
					"Semi unsupervised learning",
					"Supervised learning",
					"Reinforcement learning",
					"Unsupervised learning"
				]
			},
				{
					"question": "Identify the kind of learning algorithm for â€œfacial identities for facial expressions.",	"answer": 1,
					"options": [
						"Prediction",
						"Recognition patterns",
						"Recognizing anomalies",
						"Generating patterns"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "Identify the model which is trained with data in only a single batch.",					"answer": 2,
					"options": [
						"Offline learning",
						"Batch learning",
						"Both A and B",
						"None"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "What is the application of machine learning methods to a large database called?",
					"answer": 2,
					"options": [
						"Big data computing",
						"Internet of things",
						"Data mining",
						"Artificial intelligence"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "Identify the type of learning in which labeled training data is used.",
					"answer": 1,
					"options": [
						"Semi unsupervised learning",
						"Supervised learning",
						"Reinforcement learning",
						"Unsupervised learning"
					]
				}
			],
			"quizTotalNumbers": 5
		},
		{
			"quizName": "Spring Boot Quiz",
			"quizQuestions": [{
				"question": "Which are the modules of core container?",
				"answer": 0,
				"options": [
					"Beans, Core, Context, SpEL",
					"Core, Context, ORM, Web",
					"Core, Context, Aspects, Test",
					"Bean, Core, Context, Test"
				]
			},
				{
					"question": "What is singleton scope?",
					"answer": 0,
					"options": [
						"This scopes the bean definition to a single instance per Spring IoC container.",
						"This scopes the bean definition to a single instance per HTTP Request.",
						"This scopes the bean definition to a single instance per HTTP Session.",
						"This scopes the bean definition to a single instance per HTTP Application/ Global session."
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "What is default scope of bean in Spring framework?",
					"answer": 0,
					"options": [
						"singleton",
						"prototype",
						"request",
						"session"
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "What is constructor mode of autowiring?",
					"answer": 3,
					"options": [
						"Autowiring by property name. Spring tries to match and wire its properties with the beans defined by the same names in the configuration file.",
						"Spring first tries to wire using autowire by constructor, if it does not work, Spring tries to autowire by byType",
						"Autowiring by property type. Spring tries to match and wire a property if its type matches with exactly one of the beans name in configuration file.",
						"Similar to byType, but type applies to constructor arguments. If there is not exactly one bean of the constructor argument type in the container, a fatal error is raised."
					]
				},
				{
					"question": "What is ContextRefreshedEvent event?",
					"answer": 3,
					"options": [
						"This event is published when the Servlet Context is either initialized or refreshed",
						"This event is published when the HTTP Request is received.",
						"This event is published when the HTTP Response is returned",
						"This event is published when the ApplicationContext is either initialized or refreshed"
					]
				}
			],
			"quizTotalNumbers": 5
		}
	]
}